‎The box office has
‎really been booming this year.
‎The first half of the year was swept up
‎in the‎ Friend ‎craze.
‎"You go to Hawaii."
‎Heading into the second half of the year,
‎My Sassy Girl‎'s dominating the box office.
‎Gyeon-woo!
‎Our first song today is
‎"I Believe" by Shin Seung-hun!
‎WILD SING
‎Look, that guy's dancing.
‎Wow, what's he doing?
‎What is he doing?
‎What's your name again?
‎Dance Machine, or DM for short.
‎My name's Hwang Hyun-woo.
‎So you're 18?
‎I'm 19.
‎You look so young.
‎What do you eat to stay so young?
‎I've enjoyed pork rinds since I was a kid.
‎Would you like to hear me sing?
‎I already know how well you can sing.
‎I can tell your vocal range
‎just from talking to you.
‎I really want to be
‎a dance-pop singer.
‎Being a singer isn't anything special.
‎Anyone can make it
‎if they meet the right producer.
‎Train with me for just a year,
‎and we'll take over the music industry.
‎What? You don't want that?
‎No, it's not that. It's just...
‎I'm so honored, I can hardly believe it.
‎All right.
‎I can't pass this up!
‎We've only just met,
‎but I think we're really going to click.
‎I'm excited!
‎I'm a bit embarrassed to say this,
‎but I wasn't expecting much.
‎The practice room's in this huge building?
‎I'll really give it my all--
‎Where are you going?
‎That's the wrong building.
‎SAMWOO ENTERTAINMENT AGENCY
‎Oh, it looks very different
‎from the outside.
‎It's clean and decent inside.
‎I'll do my absolute best--
‎Where are you wandering off to?
‎It's down here.
‎YONGGU RECORDS
‎The other members are waiting
‎behind that door.
‎You should not fear
‎the journey to success.
‎What are you waiting for?
‎Go on and open the door.
‎Drive the sound in!
‎Baby!
‎Yo!
‎Drive the sound in!
‎Gu Sang-gu!
‎Let's go!
‎Hey, that's good enough.
‎It's driving straight in.
‎Take it down a notch.
‎Where's Do-mi?
‎Who's this?
‎Say hello.
‎He'll be training with you guys.
‎Dance Machine, or DM for short.
‎I'm Hwang Hyun-woo.
‎Meet Do-mi and Sang-gu.
‎Do-mi sings, and Sang-gu raps.
‎Hyun-woo, you'll sing and dance
‎as the all-rounder.
‎Why do we need another vocalist?
‎He's a sub-vocalist.
‎I thought we were a rap-heavy,
‎old-school hip-hop crew.
‎Plans have changed.
‎You are now a trio,
‎a co-ed trio!
‎A trio?
‎How could you suddenly change...
‎A trio means
‎we split the payouts three ways.
‎What are you staring at?
‎Want a slap?
‎Oh, damn.
‎He promised me
‎A rap-heavy old-school hip-hop crew
‎He lied, now he's just dancing around
‎Jeez, that's his rap?
‎I've got your debut song,
‎so let's listen together.
‎Everyone, together
‎"LOVE IS" DEMO
‎This place is dangerous.
‎What do you think?
‎Pretty dope, right?
‎How much did you pay for this?
‎This isn't hip-hop.
‎Now that we've got the song,
‎we'll need to bring in a choreographer.
‎Leave that...
‎to me.
‎1ST ALBUM PROMOTION
‎Don't be nervous about the cameras
‎and staff watching, okay?
‎And don't let the audience get to you.
‎You're so damn chatty. What, you nervous?
‎My pastor said he was super nervous
‎giving his first sermon,
‎but told himself this.
‎"Everyone here is
‎a goddamn idiot except me."
‎After that, his fear was gone.
‎A pastor calling his congregation idiots?
‎What kind of church is that?
‎-Hey, I think it's working.
‎-Right?
‎They're all goddamn idiots.
‎Yo, they're all goddamn idiots.
‎Yo, they're all babies!
‎-Hey, just say it in your head.
‎-Say it in your head!
‎All right, let's go.
‎Wait! Hold up.
‎Hyun-woo, the dancer!
‎Do-mi, the singer!
‎Sang-gu, the rapper!
‎-Triangle!
‎-Let's go!
‎-Yes!
‎The trio set to take over the music scene
‎with high-energy, powerful dance!
‎Here's Triangle's debut stage,
‎"Love Is."
‎"LOVE IS" BY TRIANGLE
‎TOP 10 MUSIC
‎Yo
‎"LOVE IS" RISING FAST
‎ROOKIE TRIO
‎TAKES THE MUSIC SCENE BY STORM
‎Everybody!
‎SWEEPS MUSIC SCENE
‎TEEN FANBASE FORMS ON DEBUT
‎Come on, now!
‎Come on, now! Let me hear you say
‎What's up? Say Triangle
‎Say Triangle
‎Meeting you
‎Was the greatest stroke of luck
‎When I look back
‎On all my days
‎The more I get to know you
‎The more scared I get
‎How much of it did you ever really mean?
‎No way, what if you do this?
‎What if you do that?
‎I bet that's what you're thinking
‎It's so obvious
‎Will you just stop and answer me?
‎It's not time yet, I mean right now
‎You shouldn't do that
‎You shouldn't do this
‎-Why is it so complicated, baby
‎Love is, why is it, why is it
‎So hard?
‎Even though every day, every day
‎You still make me laugh and cry
‎That it will last forever
‎That it will go on
‎Promise me, my love
‎Oh, my love
‎All my people say, ho!
‎Put your hands up in the air, yo!
‎-Say, hey, ho!
‎-Hey, ho!
‎What's love? Love is
‎What even is love? Love is
‎One, two, three, let's go!
‎DANCE MACHINE HYUN-WOO
‎BYEON DO-MI ROCKS
‎ONLY YOU, HWANG HYUN-WOO
‎Hey! Over here!
‎Over here!
‎2ND ALBUM PROMOTION
‎Why do we have
‎three official balloon colors?
‎They're the three primary colors of light,
‎red, green, and blue.
‎They burst onto the scene a year ago,
‎now up for number one
‎as soon as their second album dropped.
‎One, two, three.
‎-Hello!
‎-Hello! We are
‎-Triangle!
‎I heard the leader, Hyun-woo,
‎wrote and composed all the songs
‎for this album.
‎I pushed through the pain of creation,
‎all for the fans.
‎So can we call you
‎a singer-songwriter now?
‎TOP 10 MUSIC, UP FOR #1
‎TRIANGLE
‎And Do-mi, I heard
‎you underwent special vocal training.
‎Yes, that's right.
‎I always want to do better,
‎so I never even take a day off.
‎I'm very impressed by your passion.
‎Yo, check it out. Peace!
‎All right, that's it
‎for my interview with Triangle.
‎-Triangle!
‎-Thank you!
‎And joining us is
‎Ballad Prince Choi Seong-gon,
‎also up for number one
‎alongside Triangle.
‎Hello, Seong-gon.
‎You've held the number 2 spot
‎for 38 weeks, setting a new record.
‎Could you say a few words to your fans?
‎Holding number 2
‎for 38 consecutive weeks,
‎I'm your forever shining knight,
‎Choi Seong-gon.
‎My fans are the reason I exist.
‎-This is a secret, but the truth is,
‎-Yes.
‎I'm actually a big fan of theirs.
‎Triangle, love you!
‎Love!
‎Shit! Goddamn it.
‎Troy, Try, or whatever they're called.
‎They're up for number one?
‎-I worked my ass off to get here, damn it.
‎-Seong-gon, stand by.
‎-Thanks.
‎-Love you.
‎Man, it's so damn hard
‎to act friendly and everything.
‎You wrote and composed every song?
‎You can't even read sheet music.
‎Since I'm the leader, that's how
‎Mr. Park wants to promote the album.
‎What can I do?
‎What am I then, just a filler?
‎Yeah, that's what you are,
‎a filler member.
‎You bastard!
‎How dare you, you filler!
‎If you're arguing, take it outside.
‎-Cheeseball's singing.
‎-At number 2 for 38 consecutive weeks!
‎The relentless ballad prince
‎Choi Seong-gon.
‎He's going for number one again today
‎with "I Like You."
‎I like you
‎I like you because you're pretty
‎Because you're pretty
‎I like you
‎I like you because you're kind
‎Because you're kind
‎I like you
‎I like you so much I could die
‎-‎I like you
‎-I like you too!
‎-‎You like me too
‎-So handsome!
‎We like each other
‎I just
‎Like you
‎Because you're you
‎-We love you!
‎-You're so cool!
‎Shout it out
‎-Shout it out, shout it out
‎LOVE YOU, TRIANGLE
‎THE BEST IN THE UNIVERSE
‎Now, we're down to
‎the number one announcement.
‎-Dance Machine Hwang Hyun-woo!
‎-Based on album sales,
‎performance scores,
‎-‎I like you
‎-and live ARS votes,
‎who will take number 1
‎on this week's ‎Top 10 Music‎?
‎Who will it be,
‎Triangle or Choi Seong-gon?
‎Triangle, Choi Seong-gon.
‎Choi Seong-gon, Triangle.
‎CHOI SEONG-GON
‎TRIANGLE
‎All right,
‎the final scores have been tallied.
‎Top 10 Music,‎ second week of March.
‎Number...
‎two goes to Choi Seong-gon!
‎Triangle takes number one!
‎Congratulations!
‎Tell us how you feel.
‎I really had no idea
‎we'd take number one
‎with the first song I ever wrote.
‎We love you all, our RGB Army!
‎#1 "SHOUT IT OUT" BY TRIANGLE
‎We'll continue to work hard
‎to bring you even better music.
‎We won't let you down. Thank you.
‎Now, we'll wrap up the show
‎with Triangle's encore performance.
‎We'll be back next week.
‎-Bye, everyone.
‎A party for getting number one once?
‎TOP 10 MUSIC NO. 1
‎I mean, how...
‎How did that absolute trainwreck of a song
‎get number one?
‎I'm going home.
‎Gon, wait!
‎You see, everyone from
‎the broadcast station is here.
‎The CEO said to stay and meet everyone.
‎-Tell him to screw himself.
‎-Wait.
‎The director is considering
‎pushing you for number one next week.
‎If you fail again,
‎that's 40 weeks at number 2.
‎You think I have no pride?
‎Producer?
‎Is the producer...
‎Is the producer or the broadcast director...
‎Director?
‎I'm sorry.
‎Producer?
‎-Are you in there--
‎-Go on in, man.
‎Thanks.
‎I was told
‎I'd find the director and producer here.
‎They'll be here in a minute.
‎Just smoke and wait.
‎Hey, what's the matter? Don't do that.
‎I like you
‎You're my number one.
‎You really deserve number one.
‎Number 2 for 39 weeks straight?
‎Number one, Choi Seong-gon.
‎-You're the prince.
‎-I'm telling you, you're the best.
‎The Ballad Prince.
‎At number 2 for 39 weeks straight?
‎I like you so much I could die
‎Did you talk to him about our payout?
‎Come on, our money.
‎Our money.
‎Did you have the money talk with him?
‎Why are you on my case about this?
‎Because you're the leader.
‎Hey, Hyun-woo.
‎Oh, congratulations.
‎-This is wild, man. Seriously.
‎-Hey.
‎-That was so cool.
‎-Thanks.
‎Who are you again?
‎Oh, I'm with those boys over there.
‎We're Megaton.
‎I'm Na Tae-poong.
‎He's in Megaton?
‎We agreed to keep it casual last time.
‎Excuse me.
‎Someone pooped in front of the men's room.
‎Can you clean it up?
‎That's not my poop.
‎Sang-gu, he's not a server.
‎He's Megaton's...
‎Jang-poong!
‎Sorry, my bad.
‎It's Tae-poong.
‎Na Tae-poong.
‎Why don't you go by Jang-poong instead?
‎It's a better name.
‎That's a great idea.
‎Right?
‎Congratulations, man. You were amazing.
‎Seriously, you looked really cool.
‎Hello, Mr. Park.
‎I'm Megaton's Na--
‎My babies, why are you sitting around?
‎Go party it up and have fun.
‎Well, Mr. Park...
‎About what we talked about the other day.
‎The payout?
‎We still haven't gotten any payout
‎from our first album last year.
‎You know how it is.
‎These things take time.
‎You see, it's just how the system works.
‎Your payouts have just been deferred.
‎From an accounting perspective,
‎your money's in circulation right now.
‎I'm getting a call. I'll be right back.
‎Damn it.
‎You saw that, right?
‎I spoke up as the leader.
‎If I don't get my payout,
‎I'm coming for you first. You got that?
‎Hey, why didn't you guys
‎answer your phones?
‎We've got a big problem.
‎What's this?
‎It's all over the news.
‎What? "Debauched" and "hedonistic"?
‎All we did was
‎have a few drinks and have fun.
‎Jeez, that's gross!
‎What the... My gosh.
‎What is that? Has he lost his mind?
‎Wait, this idiot...
‎Why the hell
‎did he get naked at our party?
‎-Is it true that you used drugs?
‎-Did you engage in any indecent acts?
‎-No, it wasn't me.
‎-Do you deny the allegations?
‎If you used drugs, who did you do it with?
‎-Was this your first time?
‎-You're being accused of...
‎Earlier, Choi Seong-gon was seen
‎entering the police station
‎for questioning.
‎-Last night, Mr. Choi...
‎-Did you two take anything?
‎You took something, didn't you?
‎You did. I can totally tell!
‎Hey, he took something.
‎This prick took something too.
‎Come on, man.
‎I don't even take herbal medicine.
‎I knew that idiot was bad news,
‎even down to his hair parting.
‎Hey, did you get it sorted out?
‎The popular co-ed group Triangle has been
‎caught up in plagiarism allegations.
‎Huh?
‎The title track of their second album,
‎composed by Hwang Hyun-woo,
‎has been accused of
‎plagiarizing a popular Bulgarian song.
‎Let's take a listen.
‎Shout it out
‎I don't hear any similarities, do you?
‎The first one was our song, right?
‎No, the second one.
‎Or was it the first one?
‎They sounded identical.
‎Triangle's agency, Yonggu Records,
‎has yet to release an official statement...
‎What a beautiful day.
‎The day I first met you,
‎the sky looked just like this.
‎There's something beautiful about the way
‎a man walks away when it's time to leave.
‎No, you can't leave.
‎You need to sort this mess out!
‎Adios.
‎Hello?
‎Don't take this the wrong way
‎and hear me out.
‎It's not just because of what's happened.
‎I was starting to feel
‎a lot of limitations being in a group,
‎but I got a good offer.
‎From who, Do-mi?
‎Was it Mr. Hong?
‎Did you tell him about me?
‎No, I did not.
‎I can't believe you guys!
‎Who is it?
‎Just a comment, please!
‎Did you really copy that song?
‎-Hyun-woo!
‎-Just a comment!
‎-Aren't you going to release a statement?
‎-Just a moment!
‎-Is it really true?
‎-Why did you...
‎Hiding from us won't solve anything!
‎Hyun-woo! Just one comment, please.
‎What the hell is going on?
‎Yes, this must be a dream.
‎One blink,
‎and I'll wake up from this nightmare.
‎PRESENT DAY
‎"I never wanted to embarrass myself
‎in front of my boyfriend."
‎"But one day, a crisis struck."
‎"It was at our very first meeting
‎with his parents."
‎"Guess what happened?"
‎"I ended up sitting on his dad's lap!"
‎HE THINKS IT'S FUNNY
‎CAN'T STAND HIS LAUGH
‎WHO'S THIS GUY? JUST SOME DUDE?
‎Hyun-woo.
‎You know, I was a huge fan of Triangle.
‎Yeah, I could tell.
‎The way all four of you hit every move
‎in sync back then was so cool.
‎There were three of us.
‎Oh, three, right.
‎You were the top trio boy group
‎in the game.
‎We were a co-ed group.
‎Bastard.
‎What?
‎I said "guest."
‎I'm a permanent cast member,
‎and you're a bas...
‎I mean, guest.
‎"Guest."
‎Thanks for everything.
‎Is the lineup getting shuffled?
‎-Is the show getting canceled?
‎-Oh, of course not.
‎Not with the high ratings we're getting.
‎So it's just me who's getting cut?
‎Blame it on my incompetence.
‎Mr. Oh.
‎You know this is
‎the only show I do right now.
‎You have another show on cable.
‎I got cut from that show
‎over six months ago.
‎We're not close enough
‎for me to know those things.
‎We can just get closer from now on.
‎We're the same age.
‎I'm a year older.
‎Bro, what's the reason?
‎What did I do wrong, bro?
‎You've been out of the scene for so long
‎that people don't know you enough.
‎Comments have been blowing up, asking
‎why we keep bringing in a non-celebrity.
‎Me? A non-celebrity?
‎You should've
‎at least done a variety show.
‎Megaton's Na Tae-poong
‎took off on variety,
‎and now he's everywhere.
‎He's even done several commercials.
‎See you around then.
‎But...
‎Jeez.
‎"Non-celebrity"?
‎Me, a non-celebrity?
‎Yes, non-celebrity speaking.
‎This is he, non-celebrity Hwang Hyun-woo.
‎Who?
‎Producer Gong Ji-tae?
‎Of course, I know!
‎I'm a huge fan
‎of his variety shows.
‎A concert
‎in support of
‎Gangwon's Expo hosting bid?
‎It'll be broadcast live nationwide
‎in two weeks.
‎A few teams have backed out,
‎so I called you.
‎Oh, but...
‎Can't I go solo?
‎I perform solo at events these days.
‎Mr. Gong wants the original members
‎perform the original song,
‎without remix or rearrangement.
‎Are you guys still on bad terms?
‎Yeah.
‎Sorry?
‎I mean, no. It's just that...
‎It's just too sudden to contact them
‎and ask if they can perform.
‎We're planning a music variety show
‎with the groups from this concert.
‎In the second half of the year.
‎A variety show?
‎This would be a good opportunity for you.
‎We'll do it, all three of us.
‎Darn it.
‎Hyun-woo.
‎Hwang Hyun-woo.
‎Man, this is wild!
‎How have you been?
‎-Hey.
‎-How have you been, man?
‎Do I know you?
‎It's me, Megaton's Na Tae-poong.
‎I recognized you right away.
‎-Come on, I'm on everything these days.
‎-Oh, Jang...
‎I mean, Tae-poong.
‎Hey, it's been so long.
‎-I know. I guess you've been...
‎-Yeah.
‎taking a break from shows.
‎I'm a singer, after all.
‎I got an offer to perform at a concert.
‎You know Gong Ji-tae, right?
‎He's directing it.
‎So you're doing the show
‎that I turned down?
‎That's great, seriously.
‎My schedule's been packed lately.
‎I'm so exhausted
‎from all the events and shows.
‎Seriously, it's just so...
‎Hey, what's the next thing on my schedule?
‎You're going home.
‎Yeah, I finally get to take a break.
‎-Oh, man.
‎-Right.
‎All right then.
‎-Take it easy.
‎-Yeah.
‎-See you.
‎-Bye.
‎MEGATON BAR
‎He was practically invisible back then.
‎I really had no idea
‎we'd take number one
‎with the first song I ever wrote.
‎We love you all, our RGB Army!
‎Lung cancer, 100 million won.
‎Liver cancer, another 100 million.
‎Most cancer riders
‎separate major and minor cancers,
‎but we do not.
‎We don't make that distinction at all.
‎So no matter the type of cancer,
‎once you're diagnosed,
‎your life hits the jackpot
‎from that moment on.
‎Oh, I'm sorry.
‎It's not a jackpot if you get sick.
‎Sorry, one moment.
‎Sorry about that.
‎-What I meant is...
‎-I need to use the restroom.
‎Yes, of course. Please, go ahead.
‎Man, who's calling?
‎Yes, Gu Sang-gu speaking.
‎What the hell? This bastard...
‎Why's he... Huh?
‎Stop calling, you bastard.
‎Does this prick
‎still think he's the leader?
‎Asshole.
‎Why'd this jerk
‎suddenly go to the restroom?
‎Is he taking a dump?
‎It's always those idiots
‎who have to poop when they're out...
‎Read it forward, it's Gu Sang-gu
‎Read it backward, still Gu Sang-gu
‎Gu Sang-gu, the unstoppable rapper
‎You crazy little...
‎You really came all the way to my place.
‎You said to come meet you at your place.
‎Yeah, only if you had a death wish.
‎See? You did tell me to come over.
‎Sang-gu, my man. Let's do it.
‎A concert in support of
‎Gangwon's Expo hosting bid!
‎Shut up and get lost.
‎Come on, you really were
‎the best rapper out there.
‎Let's take the stage again.
‎Don't you remember
‎what you said to me back then?
‎You left me to take the fall
‎for that plagiarism scandal alone,
‎and now what?
‎You're selling me insurance?
‎Wait! I'm sorry.
‎Hyun-woo, I'm starving.
‎My stomach keeps growling at me.
‎It won't stop talking to me. "Growl!"
‎"Growl!" My stomach won't stop growling.
‎Get lost.
‎Don't ever show up in front of me again.
‎You said never to show up
‎in front of you again!
‎Come on!
‎That's why I showed up in front of you.
‎Sang-gu.
‎We've both hurt each other once,
‎so let's put it behind us now, okay?
‎Let's get back together.
‎Triangle!
‎What... Hey!
‎Long time no see, Sang-gu.
‎I almost forgot your face.
‎Mr. Ko, I'm really sorry.
‎I should've been in touch.
‎Who's he? A tagalong?
‎He was with him, so we brought him along.
‎Are you two close?
‎Well,
‎we're close enough
‎that he'd gladly take up the offer
‎if I asked him to perform with me
‎at the Gangwon Expo concert.
‎-We're about that close.
‎-So...
‎you're close enough
‎to share some real pain, right?
‎No, not quite. Take care, sir.
‎-Sang-gu.
‎-Yes?
‎When are you paying me back?
‎How much can you make
‎selling insurance anyway?
‎Mr. Ko, I'm selling insurance
‎to rebuild my credit.
‎Once my credit's back, I'll get a loan
‎and pay you back in one shot.
‎I promise!
‎Do you...
‎really have a death wish?
‎No, I do not!
‎Please don't kill my friend.
‎-How much does he owe you?
‎-300 million.
‎-I see.
‎-Hey, wait!
‎Help me. They might really kill me.
‎You crazy bastard. Seriously, 300 million?
‎What's the Gangwon Concert about?
‎Will that make me money?
‎The producer is pretty famous.
‎If we do well,
‎we'll get a regular spot on his show,
‎perform at events, land commercials,
‎and make a lot of money.
‎Didn't Megaton's Na Tae-poong blow up
‎through variety shows too?
‎What does he do?
‎He produced my solo album.
‎That's not the only thing I funded.
‎You two.
‎Can you make a comeback?
‎Us two?
‎From now on,
‎you two will work hard to pay me back.
‎You got that?
‎Why should I?
‎Pay me back.
‎I'll do my very best, sir.
‎It hurts so much.
‎-Goodbye.
‎-Thank you.
‎Who do you think you are
‎to release a solo album?
‎I barely had any rap lines
‎in Triangle songs.
‎Do-mi the singer, you the dancer,
‎and me, the filler.
‎My psychiatrist said
‎I have a second-place complex.
‎You're the third in the group.
‎-Oh, the third...
‎-You saw a psychiatrist
‎over not getting many rap lines?
‎Don't you run your mouth about my rap.
‎Rap is my everything!
‎Fine, we'll give you more rap lines.
‎Happy now?
‎Then let me fill the intro,
‎instrumental break, and outro with my rap.
‎We'll fill every empty spot with your rap.
‎Really?
‎Oh, wow.
‎But hey, do you think Do-mi will do it?
‎She married some
‎construction company owner, right?
‎That's strange. Why didn't she invite me?
‎I couldn't go either.
‎-Really?
‎-Yeah, I was in jail.
‎I knew you'd end up doing drugs.
‎Not for drugs but for gambling.
‎Drugs are serious.
‎Do-mi!
‎Do-mi, it's you! Byeon Do-mi!
‎It's you, right?
‎It's me, Hwang Hyun-woo!
‎Hey, why did you ignore my calls?
‎Let go of me. She knows me.
‎Hey, Do-mi, Do-mi!
‎See? She knows me.
‎I don't know him. Take him away.
‎Hey, Do-mi!
‎Hey!
‎HWANG HYUN-WOO:
‎LET'S GET BACK TOGETHER FOR A CONCERT!
‎So you tried to blackmail me? How cute.
‎Blackmail? No way.
‎It's just a beautiful memory we share.
‎How did you get my address?
‎Through AI.
‎AI told you my address?
‎I upgraded to the paid version.
‎I guess money really does
‎solve all problems.
‎It'll be broadcast nationwide.
‎We just have to perform our debut song,
‎and that's it.
‎But why do we have to do it?
‎We'll relive our dreams and memories--
‎Cut the bullshit.
‎Like we have any fond memories.
‎You're right.
‎You're always right.
‎Help me out just this once.
‎I'll be honest.
‎This is my last chance.
‎Please, help me.
‎-Ms. Byeon Do-mi, please.
‎-Do you need money?
‎Yes. What?
‎There's no limit on this.
‎You can spend it all you want.
‎Want it?
‎Fine.
‎Money is important,
‎and I need to make money.
‎But money isn't everything.
‎It's my dream. Think of our RGB Army.
‎I'm serious.
‎Can't you hear it?
‎My heart's pounding with excitement.
‎I feel like my heart's about to burst.
‎-Wait.
‎-Goddammit, don't follow me.
‎If you do, I'll slap you.
‎Hey!
‎Be honest.
‎Don't you want to be on stage again too?
‎Isn't that why you came here?
‎The feeling when people went wild
‎for our dance and songs!
‎That thrill.
‎Let's get on stage just one more time.
‎Come on, Do-mi.
‎Bullshit.
‎Right.
‎Why would she?
‎She's married to a rich guy.
‎I'm not very happy with
‎Jun-hoo's new English kindergarten,
‎so he can stop going after this week.
‎And starting next week,
‎get him ready
‎for the advanced art classes.
‎If you heard me, you should answer.
‎You have no manners at all.
‎I'm sorry, Mother. I...
‎I have food in my mouth right now.
‎I'll do as you said, Mother.
‎What the...
‎Turn your head when you sneeze.
‎You have no manners.
‎Gosh, I'm sorry, Mother.
‎You drive me crazy.
‎Mr. Kang.
‎Is the tree in the yard
‎being taken care of properly?
‎The new gardener is quite skilled, ma'am.
‎Great, show me. Move me to the garden.
‎Jeez, that is not normal.
‎Is it only funny to me?
‎It's not time yet, I mean right now
‎You shouldn't do that
‎You shouldn't do this
‎-Why is it so complicated, baby
‎Love is, why is it, why is it
‎So hard?
‎Even though every day, every day
‎You still make me laugh and cry
‎That it will last forever
‎That it will go on
‎-I was so cool back then.
‎-‎Promise me my love, oh my love
‎Smile at me
‎With a face full of confidence
‎NEW MESSAGE FROM HWANG HYUN-WOO
‎With your voice
‎I love you this much
‎I love you so much
‎It's overflowing
‎They'll be okay
‎with just the two of us showing up, right?
‎If they say no to that,
‎we'll get on our knees and beg.
‎Yes, come in.
‎Hey.
‎-Hello...
‎-Nice to meet you!
‎I'm...
‎You're late. Learn to be punctual.
‎Do-mi!
‎-I'm sorry!
‎-Take a seat.
‎This is our producer.
‎Dance Machine, or DM for short.
‎I'm Hwang Hyun-woo.
‎Hello! I'm...
‎Read it forward, it's Gu Sang-gu
‎Read it backward, still Gu Sang-gu
‎A-yo, peace!
‎You want us to sing right here and now?
‎You can't do it?
‎It's not that we can't do it. It's just...
‎-We need to get in sync and--
‎-Listen.
‎This concert will be broadcast live.
‎I need to make sure you can sing
‎before I put you on stage.
‎-I can totally rap--
‎-Of course, you should hear us sing.
‎How about next week?
‎-Should I sing now?
‎-No.
‎One moment.
‎Power on.
‎What if you do this?
‎What if you do that?
‎I bet that's what you're thinking
‎It's so obvious
‎Will you just stop and answer me?
‎It's not time yet
‎-She's good.
‎-‎I mean right now
‎You shouldn't do that
‎You shouldn't do this
‎-Wow, nice.
‎-‎Why is it so complicated, baby
‎Love is, why is it, why is it
‎So hard?
‎This is my favorite part.
‎-‎Even though
‎-It's my favorite too.
‎Every day, every day
‎You still make me laugh and cry
‎That it will last forever
‎-‎That it will go on
‎-This is me.
‎-‎My love
‎-She's really good.
‎Oh, my love
‎Smile at me
‎With a face full of confidence
‎Sing to me
‎Her voice hasn't changed at all.
‎It's flawless.
‎-With your voice
‎-Is she lip-syncing?
‎Lip-syncing would be better than this!
‎My gosh!
‎What's with him?
‎I'm disappointed.
‎How are we supposed to face our fans again
‎with skills this rusty?
‎Get your acts together.
‎No, this is way better than what we--
‎-No.
‎-But...
‎It's definitely not good enough.
‎We'll start practicing together today
‎to make sure our stage is fire.
‎The Expo?
‎We Triangle will make sure
‎it happens in Gangwon, no matter what.
‎Excuse me, ma'am.
‎I'm sorry,
‎but could we add some rap lines?
‎Just a few.
‎We can't do that.
‎Just a couple?
‎Stick to the original version
‎and do a good job.
‎PROFESSIONAL HUNTER
‎WILDLIFE CONTROL SPECIALIST
‎Where's the variety show department
‎meeting room?
‎Sorry?
‎Take good care of her while I'm gone.
‎Is this it?
‎The place I was called to?
‎Who is he?
‎Who are you?
‎Are you Choi Seong-gon?
‎Are wild animals spotted
‎around here these days?
‎Wild boars, water deer.
‎You didn't tell him?
‎I tried to contact him
‎but he was so hard to reach,
‎so I just set up the meeting.
‎We're organizing a concert to support
‎Gangwon's Expo hosting bid,
‎and we'd like to have you
‎as one of the performers.
‎A concert?
‎Say that again. What did you say?
‎Well, we're organizing
‎a concert in support of
‎Gangwon's Expo hosting bid,
‎and we'd like to have you
‎as one of the performers.
‎So you're saying...
‎I can be on stage again?
‎Yes, but the concert
‎will be broadcast live,
‎and it hasn't been finalized yet, so...
‎Sir, I've been dying to sing.
‎Right, but we need to make sure
‎you can still sing on stage.
‎I like you
‎I like you because you're pretty
‎Because you're pretty
‎I like you
‎I like you because you're kind
‎Because you're kind
‎I like you
‎I like you because you're funny
‎Because you're funny
‎I like you
‎I like you so much I could die
‎You like me too
‎We like each other
‎I like you
‎You like me too
‎No.
‎This is not me.
‎This is not the shining knight,
‎Choi Seong-gon.
‎No.
‎This is exactly my style.
‎Ballads are all about skill.
‎I like you
‎I rented this studio when I'm broke.
‎Where are they?
‎Hey, where are you?
‎Hey.
‎What's all this?
‎Mr. Hong said
‎there was no space in the storage room
‎and told me to get lost with my stuff.
‎I thought he was Mr. Ko.
‎Ko for my first album, Hong for my second.
‎Bro, I wanted to prove myself.
‎What is it that you keep trying to prove?
‎Where was this taken?
‎-LA.
‎-Why there?
‎It's the home of hip-hop.
‎You know, back in our Triangle days,
‎my mom was always like,
‎"Why is my son always in the corner
‎looking like a loser?"
‎It made her so upset.
‎Let's just go inside and practice.
‎My mom said...
‎Yes, you're right. You're right, Hyun-woo.
‎Snap out of it, Gu Sang-gu!
‎Yo, baby!
‎One, two, three, four.
‎DRIVE IT IN, GU SANG-GU
‎What on earth are you up to these days?
‎Seriously!
‎Are you even listening to me?
‎Hey!
‎If you're diagnosed with lung cancer
‎You get 100 million won
‎You get money if you're sick
‎It's exciting to get money
‎Sign here and you'll get money
‎SANG-GU
‎Do-mi!
‎Gosh! What took you guys so long?
‎Hey.
‎I told you guys to send me
‎your practice videos, didn't I?
‎Why didn't you send any?
‎Hey, Sang-gu...
‎Do-mi, did you memorize the choreography?
‎More or less.
‎What? More or less?
‎Gosh, I'm hungry.
‎Let's stop at a rest stop for some food.
‎I'm sure you practiced. Yeah, I'm sure.
‎-I want a corn dog.
‎-The leader told you to, after all.
‎-A fish cake bar.
‎-I'm sure you listened.
‎And ‎tteokbokki‎ too.
‎Sure.
‎-Enjoy.
‎-Nice, thank you.
‎All right, ma'am.
‎I'm not sure
‎if this cheap food will suit your taste.
‎It's fine. I'm not totally rich yet.
‎I just live with rich people, you know?
‎You just live with rich people, huh?
‎It does make me jealous,
‎but then again, it's kind of sad too.
‎You think my life is sad?
‎That's rich coming from you.
‎You've thrown away your pride just to
‎try and make a comeback through a concert.
‎Hey, pride doesn't put food on the table.
‎And if you guys hadn't ditched
‎and abandoned me back then,
‎I'd still have some pride.
‎Abandoned? You?
‎You think we ditched you?
‎You and Sang-gu signed
‎with another agency right away.
‎Seriously, you...
‎You've got a great memory.
‎That's impressive.
‎How do you remember everything?
‎Why do you remember all that?
‎-Do you think Do-mi will stay with us?
‎-I doubt it.
‎But I guess she might change her mind
‎after performing on stage.
‎Man, Do-mi is...
‎Wait a minute.
‎I feel like I know that man,
‎but I can't remember where from.
‎Hey, he does look familiar.
‎Really?
‎Then maybe he's in showbiz?
‎Maybe.
‎Guys.
‎That's Park Yong-gu.
‎-Wait.
‎-You!
‎Park Yong-gu!
‎All right, please listen carefully.
‎This man here is not Park Yong-gu.
‎He's Mr. Emiliano Scaloni.
‎His nationality isn't Korean.
‎He's Argentine.
‎Here's his passport. Look.
‎No way.
‎You ‎are‎ Park Yong-gu. Admit it!
‎I'm not Korean. I'm Argentine!
‎You are Park Yong-gu!
‎You're Park Yong-gu of Yonggu Records
‎who fled the country with our money!
‎Do I look Korean to you?
‎You think I wouldn't recognize you
‎if you spoke in a foreign language
‎and grew a mustache?
‎-Man, that must hurt.
‎-Don't treat a foreigner like this!
‎What do you think you're doing?
‎Don't do this to me!
‎The moustache looks real though.
‎Listen to me.
‎Do you want to go to the police?
‎And press charges?
‎No police.
‎I'm a busy man.
‎I have a business, very important.
‎I don't have time
‎to go to the police station!
‎Okay, okay!
‎Welcome to Korea, Mr. Scaloni.
‎-Bye.
‎-Thank you.
‎Hey, the mess you--
‎-Hey!
‎-Easy now.
‎BMW 9841 NAVY BLUE
‎MERCEDES-BENZ 8340
‎GANGWON 165KM
‎It was him.
‎That bastard was Mr. Park.
‎Okay, let's say he's Mr. Park.
‎But what can we do now?
‎We need to take bloody revenge.
‎Whose fault is it
‎that I ended up like this?
‎Hey, I think I see his car.
‎Shit.
‎Bro, what are you doing?
‎We need to catch him!
‎-What? No, don't do it.
‎-Step on it, or we'll lose him.
‎I want my money. Step on it.
‎-No, don't. Are you crazy?
‎-Go faster.
‎-What's with you, Do-mi?
‎-Let's go, hit the gas.
‎-No, don't do it.
‎-Faster. Get closer.
‎-Floor it!
‎-You're so dead.
‎We got him.
‎-Go faster!
‎-No, stop!
‎Slow down, stop!
‎Seriously, stop!
‎Got you.
‎-We got him, right here.
‎-You'll hit his car.
‎-No, we're too close. You'll hit him.
‎-Hey!
‎What if we crash into him?
‎We have to perform! Snap out of it!
‎I know who you are!
‎Hey, Park Yong-gu!
‎I want my money! Pay us what we're owed!
‎-Oh, no.
‎-Just ram him!
‎-Have you lost your mind?
‎-Let's do it!
‎-Are you crazy? Shut up!
‎-Ram him.
‎Should I really do it?
‎-Ram him. Do it.
‎-No, don't do it!
‎-Do it.
‎-I'm doing it.
‎Don't lose your head!
‎-No!
‎-Just ram him!
‎-Now!
‎-No!
‎I told you not to do it.
‎Hyun-woo, I think you're totally screwed.
‎Oh, no.
‎What do we do?
‎-No.
‎-What do we do now?
‎No!
‎Hey!
‎-Wait!
‎-Hey, wait up!
‎Hey, Park Yong-gu?
‎He's alive. He's breathing.
‎-He's alive.
‎-He is?
‎-Should we call the ambulance?
‎-Of course we should!
‎Why are you asking me?
‎You got all worked up
‎and nearly killed him.
‎So you'd be getting arrested, not me,
‎which is why I'm asking you.
‎-I'd get arrested?
‎-Yeah.
‎Do-mi, you egged me on!
‎-Right.
‎-Oh! Hold on.
‎-I think he just looked at me.
‎-Huh?
‎What the hell?
‎Are you sure you weren't mistaken?
‎-Should I just slap him?
‎-Don't!
‎What if he's really hurt
‎and you make it worse?
‎Let's get him into the car first.
‎We'll either take him to a hospital or...
‎-Or bury him in the woods.
‎-Yes, in the woods...
‎Hey! That never even crossed my mind.
‎-My gosh.
‎-Man, he's heavy.
‎-Oh, no.
‎-You can't lose your grip!
‎-No!
‎-I had a tight grip on him!
‎-What do we do?
‎-Shit.
‎-Gosh, what do we do?
‎-Pick him up!
‎-Damn it, not again!
‎-Why do you keep losing your grip?
‎I'm not doing this.
‎-Oh, man.
‎-Was I mistaken?
‎He hasn't opened his eyes once.
‎What if he's actually dead now
‎because you kept losing your grip?
‎I was holding on tight.
‎I'm sorry! I'm a novice driver.
‎A novice?
‎And you're driving a dump truck?
‎Mister, watch where you're driving!
‎Are you okay? Are you hurt?
‎Did I kill anyone?
‎Please tell me I didn't.
‎-No, you didn't kill or hurt anyone here.
‎-Hide him.
‎Damn it.
‎Let me call the police first.
‎I'll turn myself in.
‎Put that phone down, right now!
‎What are you doing?
‎Put that down, now!
‎You're bleeding.
‎Sir, please let me call
‎my insurance company.
‎Driving can leave you a little hurt
‎or bleeding sometimes.
‎But the car's smashed in.
‎I said it's fine.
‎You're being really annoying.
‎Just go, please.
‎Hang on a second.
‎You people...
‎I know that lady.
‎Byeon...
‎Dom?
‎Rockfish?
‎How could someone's name be Rockfish?
‎Byeon Do-mi from Tambourine,
‎one of the top co-ed groups in the 2000s.
‎Right?
‎-Xylophone?
‎-We're Triangle.
‎Triangle!
‎All right.
‎I'm going to post about this online.
‎-Post what?
‎-About the generosity you showed me.
‎Yes, great idea!
‎-Go post it right now.
‎-Okay.
‎Go on, then.
‎Just go. It's fine.
‎I'm counting on that post!
‎Guys, we can get this all sorted out.
‎Just stay focused.
‎He'll post good stuff about us.
‎We just have to perform well.
‎Where did that man go?
‎Shit.
‎-Oh, what the...
‎-What happened?
‎So he wasn't dead after all.
‎There he is!
‎Park Yong-gu!
‎Stop right there!
‎I don't know you!
‎GANGWON 100KM
‎That's a size I don't see often.
‎URGENT WILDLIFE CONTROL TARGET
‎No.
‎I'm a singer, not a hunter.
‎Get it together.
‎I like you
‎Please stop following me!
‎You damn bastard!
‎Hey, let's just talk for a minute!
‎I've got something important today.
‎Let's talk this out.
‎Please stop following me!
‎You damn bastard!
‎Oh, jeez.
‎Damn, where'd he go?
‎This is driving me crazy.
‎Did I just shoot him?
‎Excuse me.
‎You're not dead, are you?
‎Oh god, you can't die.
‎Hold on.
‎Wait.
‎If I get arrested again...
‎Was this your first time? If not...
‎You're being accused of exhibitionism.
‎Any comments?
‎No.
‎Who's this prick now?
‎Who's this idiot?
‎Oh, hello.
‎Something's fishy.
‎Yes, hello.
‎Something's off about him.
‎Oh, I'm just taking a walk.
‎Me too.
‎Taking a walk, here?
‎Just out for a walk.
‎Is he out of his mind?
‎Do I know you
‎from somewhere?
‎I do feel like you look familiar.
‎Have we met before?
‎-Did you do that?
‎-It wasn't me!
‎Hey, what are you doing? Push harder.
‎It won't budge!
‎This isn't working.
‎Do-mi.
‎-I feel dizzy.
‎-You can stop now.
‎Do-mi, my head feels weird.
‎What's that clunker?
‎Hello, Hyun-woo. When are you arriving?
‎Rehearsal's about to start.
‎The producer's looking for you.
‎Oh, is he?
‎Well, we're perfectly prepared,
‎so we don't need a rehearsal.
‎You won't be late, right?
‎-Oh, of course we won't be late.
‎-Hi, Choi Seong-gon here!
‎I'm with them, and we're running late.
‎You're with Seong-gon?
‎Yes, we're on our way together.
‎Didn't he say you guys are running late?
‎Hyun-woo, you cannot be late,
‎no matter what.
‎Sorry, see you soon.
‎-Hey, what are we going to do with him?
‎-Seriously.
‎Has he been shot anywhere?
‎Look closely. I swear he's been shot.
‎I said I didn't shoot him!
‎Don't put this all on me.
‎If you're innocent,
‎the police will clear it up.
‎Let's go to the police station.
‎The police?
‎What do you mean, the police?
‎How can you say that to an old friend
‎you haven't seen in years?
‎Friend, my ass.
‎-You're the reason we disbanded!
‎-That's right.
‎-Your plagiarism scandal broke you up.
‎-Plagiarism?
‎The drugs and the plagiarism...
‎The plagiarism scandal did kill us.
‎-I mean, it's true.
‎-Oh, shit.
‎What? Did you find a bullet wound?
‎I just caught his eye.
‎Oh, he's awake?
‎Goddammit.
‎I think he's faking it.
‎If I catch his eye one more time, I swear...
‎Seobu Intersection Control,
‎emergency dispatch. Accident reported.
‎Report of a vehicle collision
‎resulting in a fall.
‎Location is San 58,
‎Jucheon-ro, Seobu-gu, Gangwon.
‎Confirm situation on scene and report.
‎We're arrived at the scene.
‎Vehicle confirmed.
‎License plate number, 8340...
‎That's the Mercedes from earlier!
‎We have a police car behind us.
‎Hide. Get down!
‎What is that?
‎PROFESSIONAL HUNTER
‎WILDLIFE CONTROL SPECIALIST
‎Is he out of his mind?
‎Why are you ducking? You need to drive!
‎Is this a Tesla?
‎Hey, pull over for a minute.
‎I said, pull over.
‎Are you out of your mind?
‎What's going on here?
‎Is there something down there?
‎You're those guys from earlier.
‎-Oh, hello.
‎-Hello.
‎We've got a performance today,
‎so we're in a hurry.
‎We're singers, you see.
‎Don't you recognize me?
‎-Allure Queen Byeon Do-mi. Remember?
‎-Peace.
‎Sure.
‎Who's this guy here?
‎I'm a singer too.
‎Love you.
‎What's that?
‎What is?
‎What is that?
‎This? It was in the car.
‎Freeze!
‎What's happening?
‎-Drop the gun and put your hands up.
‎-Drop the gun and hands up!
‎Please, I'm sorry!
‎-That rifle's his. This guy.
‎-Yes, that's right.
‎Yes, I'm a hunter.
‎-Not a singer?
‎-I work as a hunter now.
‎-Move those clothes aside.
‎-Okay, all right.
‎-No, no.
‎-No.
‎What the hell!
‎You killed that foreigner!
‎No, he's pretending to be unconscious.
‎He's totally fine.
‎Hands off the wheel, step out of the car.
‎This is live ammo.
‎We're getting out.
‎We just need to make it to the stage.
‎What stage?
‎You're under arrest for murder!
‎"Arrest"?
‎I cannot get arrested.
‎Get them!
‎What the hell are you doing?
‎I lost 20 long years of my life.
‎I can't live like that again.
‎Snap out of it.
‎-Do this, and we really can't perform.
‎-Hey.
‎Are you seriously worried
‎about the performance?
‎Quiet, everyone.
‎Yes, Ms. Yang, we're almost there.
‎Oh, we're now...
‎We're downtown in Gangwon.
‎Hey, did you pass out?
‎Seriously, the producer
‎is furious right now.
‎Oh, is he?
‎Hey, Gu Sang-gu! Seriously...
‎This is a live broadcast.
‎You can't be this late.
‎If you're late for rehearsal,
‎he'll replace you.
‎What? There's a backup?
‎Hey, tell them not to bother coming.
‎Hey, forget it! Don't come!
‎Hurry. Get here as soon as you can!
‎I swear, we won't be late.
‎We're really close.
‎-Forget it. Don't come!
‎-Just hurry.
‎Step on it.
‎You crazy idiots, just give up already.
‎Step on it, now!
‎Let's go!
‎They've got their siren on!
‎Are you really going to shoot?
‎I told you, I saw a dead man in the car.
‎They're real murderers.
‎Wee-woo, police car's coming.
‎-Hey, stop the car.
‎-No.
‎We don't have time. We have to perform.
‎We have to catch them. Close in now!
‎Those crazy bastards.
‎Pull over!
‎Hey, watch out!
‎Are they crazy? We didn't do anything.
‎You're the craziest one here, damn it!
‎Hey, we didn't do anything wrong.
‎It's their own fault
‎for firing recklessly.
‎You're sure we can perform today, right?
‎I really need to do my new rap.
‎My mom's been waiting so long for this.
‎Wait, why did you write a new rap?
‎You didn't know? I'm filling the intro,
‎interlude, and outro with my rap.
‎What the hell are you saying?
‎-No, we'll stick to the original version.
‎-Yeah.
‎The original version?
‎So you lied to me?
‎Let's just get there first, all right?
‎Next time,
‎you can rap as much as you want.
‎Next time? So you lied to me.
‎Let's just focus on the performance
‎and do a good job, okay?
‎You lied to me, you jerk!
‎-You bastard! How could you...
‎-Hey.
‎-Hey!
‎-Is that really important now?
‎-Let's just get there first, okay?
‎-No!
‎Son of a bitch!
‎That's enough!
‎-Hey, Hwang Hyun-woo!
‎-Come on.
‎You're supposed to be the leader,
‎but you can't even fix anything!
‎And you, Gu Sang-gu.
‎I wouldn't even complain
‎if you were actually a good rapper.
‎Gosh, what am I even doing
‎with you idiots?
‎Damn it, I need a smoke.
‎What about my third album then? Oh, shit.
‎You've signed for another album?
‎I need to show them.
‎Show what? What the hell is your problem?
‎What kind of lunatic told you
‎to make another album?
‎Which scumbag producer was it?
‎My dad.
‎What?
‎My dad wanted to help me,
‎so he took out a loan and sold our house...
‎Oh, goodness.
‎-Just to help this useless son...
‎-Oh, boy.
‎It's all my fault.
‎-What's going on?
‎-Huh?
‎What's wrong with the car?
‎-Hey!
‎-Stop!
‎Hey, stop!
‎Stop!
‎Dad!
‎Yes, Ms. Yang. We're almost there.
‎-We'll--
‎-‎Are you insane?
‎How can you be late
‎to a live show I'm directing?
‎You're never working with me again.
‎Got it?
‎No, sir, please...
‎I'm hanging up!
‎Hey, where's the backup?
‎They're on their way.
‎Who? Someone famous?
‎There they are.
‎You know them, right?
‎Kong Kong Girls.
‎Tell them to just turn around and leave.
‎-Yes, you can go.
‎-I'm sorry. Please go.
‎Can't you get off those things and walk?
‎-Sir.
‎-That's too much.
‎Na Tae-poong's in Sancheok now.
‎If he leaves now,
‎he'll make it in time for our finale.
‎-Na Tae-poong?
‎-Yes.
‎-Tell him to come now. Hurry!
‎-Okay, got it.
‎It's all over now.
‎I've lost my last chance at a comeback.
‎It's over now.
‎They say
‎everyone gets three chances in life.
‎They're wrong.
‎Who's generous enough
‎to give you three chances?
‎You should've seized it
‎when it first came.
‎I knew this would happen
‎I shouldn't have gotten my hopes up
‎I knew we were going to fail anyway
‎My shattered beat
‎The rhyming verse
‎I'll be spitting as I die
‎Are you okay? Snap out of it, man!
‎Snap out of it?
‎You snap out of it, bang, bang
‎Your singing sucks just as much as my rap
‎Hey, your rap sucks big-time.
‎You call that a rhyme?
‎Freestyle is all the same
‎If that's freestyle, I could do it too
‎You just have to match the last syllable
‎That's it
‎Maybe I could be a rapper too
‎And quit being a ballad singer
‎I think I'm pretty good
‎Love you
‎Screw off, weirdo.
‎Oh, I can freestyle rap
‎Freestyle
‎You're doing it freestyle
‎I can do it too
‎I'm just winging it, winging it
‎And it turns into rap, yo
‎You're nowhere near my level.
‎I'm offended, so cut it out.
‎Yo
‎Whose fault is it
‎That we're in this mess now, yo
‎Why is our leader keeping his mouth shut?
‎Pass!
‎Hey, leader!
‎Say something. What now?
‎Hey, what's with you?
‎I think they hit their heads in the crash.
‎They've both lost their minds.
‎Yes, Ms. Yang.
‎We're really almost there.
‎-‎Really?
‎-We're outside the venue.
‎If you're not here, we're replacing you.
‎Yes, see you in a bit.
‎You only get three chances in life?
‎That's way too few. That's not fair.
‎It's only natural
‎to fail three times in life.
‎Shouldn't we get dozens of chances?
‎Don't you agree?
‎Even if war breaks out or aliens attack,
‎we're taking the stage today!
‎You got that, Byeon Do-mi?
‎What?
‎You left the house for once.
‎You need to get on stage!
‎-Hell yeah.
‎-And you, Gu Sang-gu.
‎You can't let that new rap go to waste!
‎No way, I have to do it. Let's go!
‎Why are you all quiet, you little shit?
‎Don't you want to perform?
‎I want to, you little shit!
‎But we don't have a car.
‎What's that? Is that a boat?
‎There's a car passing by every minute!
‎We've got no time and nothing to lose.
‎Get your stuff!
‎We've got nothing to lose...
‎Wait, this is yours.
‎My gosh. Hey, this is wrong.
‎Hyun-woo.
‎I know we all want to perform,
‎but we can't commit a crime!
‎Don't you know what hitchhiking is?
‎Don't you know?
‎-Here.
‎-Jeez.
‎What do we do with him?
‎I swear, I caught his eye earlier.
‎He's just pretending to be passed out.
‎But why's he still keeping up the act?
‎Mr. Park.
‎If you're doing this
‎because you know you owe us money,
‎let's just call it even now.
‎What can we do about it now anyway?
‎Want me to put it in writing
‎that we'll let bygones be bygones?
‎-Yes, do that!
‎-What the...
‎-Oh, shit!
‎-I told you!
‎-Jeez.
‎-Oh, boy.
‎What happened to my neck?
‎Listen, guys.
‎Old-school K-pop is taking off again
‎in South America.
‎I'll pick a few groups
‎and break them into that market.
‎Why didn't I know
‎you were performing today?
‎You haven't changed at all.
‎Let's go hit the stage.
‎Let's go.
‎Here, please!
‎Love you!
‎Put your hands in the air!
‎-You're under arrest for murder.
‎-Freeze!
‎Who died?
‎Don't you understand Korean?
‎I crashed my car
‎due to my own careless driving.
‎These guys here helped me.
‎You couldn't speak Korean earlier.
‎No, I just didn't want to speak it.
‎-I hadn't spoken Korean for a while.
‎-Here you go.
‎But it's coming back now.
‎Ga, na, da, ra, ma, ba, sa
‎A, ja, cha, ka, ta, pa, ha
‎I like you
‎Because you're pretty
‎-Yo.
‎-I like you
‎Read it forward, Gu Sang-gu
‎Backward, still Gu Sang-gu
‎Love is, why is it, why is it
‎So hard?
‎-‎That it will go on, promise me
‎-‎Gu Sang-gu, the unstoppable rapper
‎My love, oh my love
‎Look at me, here we go again
‎GANGWON CIVIC ARENA
‎Guys, this won't work. Let's just run.
‎Hurry! Come on!
‎Come, run!
‎This is ridiculous!
‎Come on!
‎Opportunities like this
‎don't come around often.
‎Hey!
‎Don't you want to perform?
‎Run as fast as you can!
‎Hey, come on!
‎Come on, hurry.
‎La, la, la, la, la, la
‎Wonderful liar, you are
‎These idiots!
‎-What the hell?
‎-My gosh.
‎-We're sorry.
‎-Did a war break out or something?
‎Hurry, one of you has to go up there now.
‎It's a live concert.
‎At least let us catch our breath.
‎I came in the wrong entrance.
‎He can go first.
‎-Seong-gon will go up now.
‎-I'm going first?
‎-You can just stand and sing.
‎-Just sing?
‎-You're a pro, Seong-gon.
‎-I'm a pro.
‎-I'm a pro!
‎-You're closing the show.
‎Introduce yourselves, perform,
‎and what do you say at the end?
‎-Gangwon for the Expo!
‎That shoutout is more important
‎than your performance. Got it?
‎Don't forget that, okay?
‎Hey, Ms. Yang.
‎Hey, listen.
‎-Are they in trouble or something?
‎-What?
‎Look, something must've happened.
‎They all look like shit.
‎Maybe they were in a car accident.
‎What if they caused the accident?
‎What?
‎Think about it.
‎If they caused a hit-and-run,
‎it'll be a big problem.
‎It could ruin my career.
‎Then what do we do?
‎Choi Seong-gon is on stage now.
‎The song has already started. Go now.
‎-Oh, this is my song.
‎-Yes.
‎I like you
‎-I like you
‎-How's it going?
‎-Is he back on drugs?
‎-Because you're pretty
‎I like you
‎Because you're kind
‎-Because you're kind
‎-First, drugs and now a hit-and-run...
‎I like you because you're funny
‎Sir, Na Tae-poong is here.
‎We're replacing Triangle
‎with Na Tae-poong.
‎...I could die
‎He's turning around and throwing up.
‎Man, that idiot's turning around
‎while throwing up.
‎When we met for the third time, I knew
‎That you and I felt the same way
‎-We need to hurry.
‎-Oh, sure.
‎-I got this.
‎-Okay.
‎He's going up in a moment.
‎Got it.
‎Tae-poong.
‎Hey.
‎What are you doing here?
‎I'm a singer,
‎so obviously I'm here to perform.
‎Why else?
‎What, do you think I'm here
‎to clean up poop in the bathroom?
‎The concept here is a bit old-school.
‎Because you're pretty
‎I like you
‎I like you so much I could die
‎Hyun-woo.
‎I don't think Triangle can perform today.
‎What are you talking about?
‎That's not true, right?
‎We're just following
‎the producer's instructions.
‎You go ahead. I'll be right there.
‎-Hurry.
‎-Yes, of course.
‎No, wait.
‎What was it? Was it this?
‎It was something like this, you know.
‎Oh, a triangle.
‎No one even remembers Triangle.
‎You thought you could do the finale?
‎Tae-poong.
‎This is our last chance.
‎We have to perform on this stage.
‎So please...
‎Let us perform here today.
‎Please, Tae-poong.
‎Wow, you finally got my name right.
‎It's a cool name.
‎Oh, come on.
‎Back in the day,
‎you guys treated me like I was invisible.
‎When you ran into me the other day,
‎you barely recognized me, right?
‎Well, I recognized you right away.
‎Right now, I'm way more famous than you,
‎so why didn't you recognize me?
‎You got it all wrong. The truth is...
‎We were always jealous
‎of your looks and talent,
‎so we just ignored you.
‎Bullshit!
‎You're bullshitting me
‎because you're desperate to perform.
‎We Triangle were fans of Megaton.
‎Stop bullshitting me.
‎It's true!
‎I held your hand
‎I like you
‎I like you because you're pretty
‎Because you're pretty
‎I like you
‎I like you because you're kind
‎Hey!
‎Who the hell is replacing us?
‎Is it this guy?
‎They got a trot singer?
‎Hey, they're saying we can't perform
‎because of a typhoon.
‎The weather was fine earlier.
‎Why a typhoon all of a sudden, goddamn it?
‎Shut it!
‎Don't get the wrong idea, Jang-poong.
‎I just like you...
‎Goddamn it, you guys
‎really haven't changed one bit.
‎You know what?
‎You're not performing today.
‎Okay? So just go home.
‎Wait, Jang-poong...
‎Tae-poong!
‎I finally got to perform again,
‎and I blew it.
‎I'm a ballad singer
‎who wins people over with my voice.
‎Hey, Tae-poong.
‎Tae-poong, please!
‎Tae-poong, just this once.
‎So they meant Tae-poong, not a typhoon?
‎Listen, we went through
‎utter hell today
‎just to make it here in time to perform.
‎Let's just do it.
‎What?
‎I just want to perform.
‎Why does it have to be so hard?
‎No, stop!
‎-Get them.
‎-Hey!
‎Stay with us and enjoy the concert.
‎Up next is our next performer.
‎Let me introduce the next performer.
‎This is tonight's final performance.
‎He's far too popular right now
‎to be just called a retro singer.
‎It's Megaton's...
‎Oh, I...
‎-I must've--
‎-Hello, everyone!
‎It's me, Byeon Do-mi,
‎and I'm back!
‎Read it forward, it's Gu Sang-gu
‎Backward, still Gu Sang-gu
‎Hello! I'm Triangle's leader,
‎Dance Machine, or DM for short,
‎Hwang Hyun-woo.
‎Are you guys ready
‎to get wild with Triangle?
‎Have they completely lost their minds?
‎What? I can't hear you!
‎All right! Let's get wild!
‎Everybody, put your hands up!
‎Tae-poong.
‎Make some noise!
‎Let's go!
‎This is a disaster.
‎It'll be a major on-air disaster.
‎We have to start the backing track.
‎I swear,
‎those idiots caused some kind of accident.
‎They'll end my career right here and now.
‎CONCERT IN SUPPORT OF
‎THE GANGWON EXPO 2035
‎Love is, why is it, why is it
‎So hard?
‎-Triangle
‎-Even though every day, every day
‎-You still make me laugh and cry
‎-That it will last forever
‎-Forever
‎-That it will go on, promise me
‎-My love
‎-Oh, my love
‎-Smile at me
‎-With a face full of confidence
‎-Sing to me with your angelic voice
‎-Angel
‎-I love you this much
‎-Love, love
‎Dance Machine, or DM for short.
‎My name's Hwang Hyun-woo.
‎Leave that to me.
‎-Hyun-woo, the dancer!
‎-Do-mi, the singer!
‎Sang-gu, the rapper!
‎-Triangle!
‎I love you this much
‎I love you so much it's overflowing
‎Say Triangle
‎Say Triangle!
‎Just cue the backing track.
‎The most important thing is
‎the Expo shoutout at the end.
‎The Ministry of Culture stressed it.
‎We're all finished
‎if we get on the government's bad side.
‎No, come on!
‎What?
‎My name is Gu Sang-gu
‎Read it forward, it's Gu Sang-gu
‎Read it backward, still Gu Sang-gu
‎The unstoppable rapper
‎My name is Gu Sang-gu
‎Our Gu Sang-gu
‎Rap is my everything
‎Rap is my life
‎I want to succeed
‎But reality is messed up
‎Rap is my everything
‎Rap is my life
‎I want to succeed
‎But reality is messed up
‎Are you ready?
‎Yo, check it, everybody, come on
‎Rap, Mom, Dad, they are my everything
‎Everyone laughs at me
‎And says I'm a bad rapper
‎I wanted to show them I could make it
‎So here I am, all in
‎If you laugh at Gu Sang-gu's rap
‎You'll get a spinning kick from Gu Sang-gu
‎Get ready for Gu Sang-gu's Fire Shot
‎Gu Sang-gu, coming at you at full force!
‎Meeting you
‎Was the greatest stroke of luck
‎When I look back
‎On all my days
‎The more I get to know you
‎The more scared I get
‎Do-mi, it's you! Byeon Do-mi!
‎It's you, right?
‎...did you ever really mean?
‎No way, what if you do this?
‎What if you do that?
‎I bet that's what you're thinking
‎It's so obvious
‎Will you just stop and answer me?
‎It's not time yet, I mean right now
‎You shouldn't do that
‎You shouldn't do this
‎-Why is it so complicated, baby
‎Love is, why is it, why is it
‎So hard?
‎Even though every day, every day
‎You still make me laugh and cry
‎That it will last forever
‎That it will go on
‎Promise me, my love
‎Smile at me
‎-With a face full of confidence
‎-Oh, nice. They're good.
‎-Tae-poong, are you okay?
‎-What?
‎Tae-poong, are you all right?
‎They're such nice people.
‎And their song's awesome.
‎Thank you,
‎Tambourine.
‎Check it out now
‎Yo
‎Gu Sang-gu
‎I got a feeling, yes I
‎Whoever you are, you can't stop me
‎Don't stop, stop, stop
‎We're going nonstop
‎Come into my, come into my
‎Come into my, my, my heart
‎One, two, three, let's go!
‎No way, what if you do this?
‎What if you do that?
‎I bet that's what you're thinking
‎It's so obvious
‎Will you just stop and answer me?
‎It's not time yet, I mean right now
‎You shouldn't do that
‎You shouldn't do this
‎-Why is it so complicated, baby
‎Love is, why is it, why is it
‎So hard?
‎Even though every day, every day
‎You still make me laugh and cry
‎That it will last forever
‎That it will go on
‎Promise me, my love
‎-I love you that much
‎Yo, everybody, put your hands up
‎Rap, Mom, Dad, they are my everything
‎Everyone laughs at me
‎And says I'm a bad rapper
‎I wanted to show them I could make it
‎So here I am, all in
‎If you laugh at Gu Sang-gu's rap
‎You'll get a spinning kick from Gu Sang-gu
‎Get ready for Gu Sang-gu's Fire Shot
‎Gu Sang-gu, coming at you at full force!
‎Is he really out of his mind?
‎I think I set a record today.
‎I think I've been underestimating you
‎all this time.
‎I did it all.
‎-Dance Machine Hwang Hyun-woo!
‎-Allure Queen Byeon Do-mi!
‎-I'm hearing things now.
‎-Unstoppable Rapper Gu Sang-gu!
‎I should go see a doctor.
‎Look, in the back...
‎-Dance Machine Hwang Hyun-woo!
‎-Allure Queen Byeon Do-mi!
‎-Unstoppable Rapper Gu Sang-gu!
‎TOGETHER, WE ARE WHOLE
‎ONCE AGAIN, TRIANGLE
‎WE LOVE YOU, HWANG HYUN-WOO
‎BYEON DO-MI ROCKS
‎Did we forget something?
‎Wait a minute.
‎Guys, do the Expo shoutout!
‎Say it, now! You crazy brats.
‎-Right, the Olympics.
‎-Oh, right.
‎One, two, three.
‎-Triangle is rooting
‎-for the Gangwon Olympics!
‎Damn it, I can't believe this.
‎-I'm really sorry.
‎-Wait, am I supporting you right now?
‎-I'll be in touch.
‎-No, don't contact me.
‎Call me.
‎-Okay, thank you!
‎-Thank you!
‎Is that Park Yong-gu?
‎I love your style.
‎Fans overseas will love you.
‎This is me.
‎What song did you sing?
‎I know every singer there is.
‎-He's--
‎-Don't you know about me?
‎I know you very well.
‎I'm the singer.
‎Can't you tell from what I'm wearing?
‎I'm clearly the singer.
‎You cried, didn't you? Are you happy now?
‎This is a disgrace to the family!
‎Come here, now!
‎Hey, Do-mi.
‎Don't go.
‎Let's stay together and do this together.
‎Does that life make you happy?
‎You look much happier on stage.
‎You won't live like that forever, right?
‎What are you doing?
‎Come closer, right now.
‎-Stay out of this, woman.
‎-‎What? Woman?
‎Gosh, this is insane. This is nuts.
‎We can make a lot of money too.
‎We're in the golden age
‎of K-pop right now.
‎It's better to be a singer
‎than marry into wealth now.
‎But her in-laws are probably loaded.
‎Come on, how rich could they be?
‎No one knows their company.
‎Their market cap is 1.3 trillion.
‎What?
‎Hey, you little shit!
‎Hurry up!
‎Yes, Mother. I'm coming.
‎Watch.
‎All that money will be mine.
‎Unbelievable. This is ridiculous!
‎She's so freaking cool.
‎-‎What were you thinking?
‎-I know, right?
‎What? Am I your friend?
‎Are you crazy?
‎Have you completely lost your mind?
‎I guess we won't see her again.
‎Wasn't it nice to get back on stage?
‎Yeah.
‎Seriously.
‎Should we keep doing this?
‎Just the two of us?
‎One, two, three, let's go!
‎No way, what if you do this?
‎What if you do that?
‎I bet that's what you're thinking
‎It's so obvious
‎Will you just stop and answer me?
‎It's not time yet, I mean right now
‎Yo, everybody, put your hands up
‎Rap, Mom, Dad, they are my everything
‎Hold that. That's great!
‎Oh, that's nice.
‎Nice.
‎A bit more intense. Your eyes!
‎Bring it up a notch!
‎Something sexy this time. Nice!
‎-Wait!
‎-I think we've got enough shots.
‎Let's call it a wrap.
‎Ms. Byeon.
‎You slackers. You need to do your job!
‎Make profits within six months,
‎or I'm breaking you up!
‎Answer me!
‎-Yes, ma'am!
‎-All right, here we go.
‎-Okay!
‎The new Triangle pose.
‎All right. One, two, three!
‎One more time. One, two, three!
‎Yo
‎Are you ready?
‎Everybody
‎Come on, now
‎Let me hear you say
‎What's up? Say Triangle
‎Say Triangle
‎Meeting you
‎Was the greatest stroke of luck
‎When I look back
‎On all my days
‎The more I get to know you
‎The more scared I get
‎How much of it did you ever really mean?
‎No way, what if you do this?
‎What if you do that?
‎I bet that's what you're thinking
‎It's so obvious
‎Will you just stop and answer me?
‎It's not time yet, I mean right now
‎You shouldn't do that
‎You shouldn't do this
‎-Why is it so complicated, baby
‎Love is, why is it, why is it
‎So hard?
‎Even though every day, every day
‎You still make me laugh and cry
‎That it will last forever
‎That it will go on
‎Promise me, my love
‎Oh, my love
‎Smile at me
‎With a face full of confidence
‎Sing to me
‎With your angelic voice
‎-I love you this much
‎-I love you so much it's overflowing
‎I love you that much
‎All my people say, ho
‎Put your hands up in the air, yo!
‎-Say, hey, ho!
‎-Hey, ho!
‎What is love? Love is
‎What even is love? Love is
‎One, two, three, let's go!
‎No way, what if you do this?
‎What if you do that?
‎I bet that's what you're thinking
‎It's so obvious
‎Will you just stop and answer me?
‎It's not time yet, I mean right now
‎You shouldn't do that
‎You shouldn't do this
‎-Why is it so complicated, baby
‎Love is, why is it, why is it
‎So hard?
‎Even though every day, every day,
‎You still make me laugh and cry
‎That it will last forever
‎That it will go on
‎Promise me, my love
‎Oh, my love
‎Smile at me
‎With a face full of confidence
‎Sing to me
‎With your angelic voice
‎-I love you this much
‎-I love you so much it's overflowing
‎I love you that much
‎Triangle's in the house
‎Shout it out
‎Shout it out, shout it out
‎Our ship is being poisoned by our greed
‎Trash piling up
‎From reckless overconsumption
‎The selective comfort of those
‎Who live only for today
‎It's destroying you and me, all of us here
‎One, two, three, four, my peace
‎Hang it up, hang it up, now
‎The world I created
‎Is coming back to get me
‎Living for today is
‎My promise to protect it
‎Can you hear me?
‎Nothing lasts forever
‎Don't run from the uncomfortable truth
‎Can you hear me?
‎Shout it out
‎Shout it out, shout it out
‎Subtitle translation by: L. Choi